http://www.zefon.com/privacy-policy

The Professionals Choicefor Air Sampling Equipment
Register
Log in
Shopping cart
(0)
You have no items in your shopping cart.
Allegro Industries
AP Buck Inc.
Blog
Need Help?
Allegro Industries
AP Buck Inc.
Blog
Need Help?
Introduction
Zefon is a manufacturer and supplier of sampling equipment used to monitor indoor environmental, occupational health and safety conditions. In order to provide information on our products, and provide a method for customers to purchase products, Zefon operates the www.zefon.com and eshop.zefon.com websites (the "Website").
This Privacy Policy informs you of our policies regarding the collection, use, and disclosure of Personal Data when you use our Website and the choices you have associated with that data. By using the Website, you agree to the collection and use of information in accordance with this policy.
Definitions
Personal Data Personal Data means personal information that can be associated with an identified or identifiable person.  “Personal Data” can include name, postal address (including billing and shipping addresses), telephone number, email address, payment card number, other financial account information, account number, date of birth, and government-issued credentials (e.g., driver’s license number, national ID, passport, Social Security number and Taxpayer ID).  Personal Data does not include information that does not identify a specific person.
Usage DataUsage Data is non-personally identifiable data collected automatically while using the Website.
Information we collect that you provide to us directly
What we collect
We only collect personally identifiable information (“Personal Data”) if you choose to provide it to us. Personal Data you provide may include, but is not limited to:
Registration information When you register on our Website by establishing an account, we will collect Personal Data as necessary to get the account established. This information includes name, address(s), telephone number, and email address.
Transaction information When you make purchases on our website, we collect information about the transaction in order to fulfill your request. This information includes name, billing address, shipping address, email address, phone number, shipping preferences and payment details. In some cases we may need to ask for additional information in order to verify legitimacy of a transaction or to help avoid fraud.
Contacting us by Email or a Contact Form on the website When you contact us by email or a contact form we use whatever personal information you provide us to assist you, and respond to your request.
Why we collect this information and how we use it
Zefon will hold any Personal Data you provide with the utmost care and will not be used in ways that you have not consented to. Personal Data you provide us will NOT be sold or rented to anyone. Our use of your Personal Data is related to us doing business with you and is outlined in this policy. Zefon uses the Personal data you provide to:
To process purchase transactions you have made on our website.
To respond to you regarding the reason you contacted us.
To provide customer support.
We may use your Personal Data to contact you with newsletters, marketing or promotional materials and other information that may be of interest to you. You may opt out of receiving any, or all, of these communications from us by following the unsubscribe link or instructions provided in any email we send.
Information we collect automatically
What we collect
We collect non-personally identifiable information about how the website is accessed and used ("Usage Data"). This Usage Data includes information such as your computer's Internet Protocol address (e.g. IP address), browser type, browser version, the pages of our website that you visit, the time and date of your visit, the time spent on those pages, the page you clicked on that linked to our website, unique device identifiers and other diagnostic data.
Why we collect this information and how we use it
Zefon International uses the non-personally identifiable information we collect automatically to:
Monitor the usage of our website.
Learn what aspects of our website customers like and dislike.
Understand statistics about how many of the visitors to our site make a purchase.
Make business decisions regarding advertising and promotions that are working.
Detect, prevent and address technical issues.
Monitor for suspicious or fraudulent activity.
Tracking Cookies
Cookies are files with a small amount of data which may include an anonymous unique identifier. Cookies are sent to your browser from a website and stored on your device. Most all modern websites today use Cookies to improve the user experience on their website. Our website is no different and uses cookies and similar tracking technologies to track the activity on our website.
Why are Cookies used?
The use of cookies allows websites to make your visit more user friendly. For example, remembering the items you placed in a shopping cart on your next visit, or remembering your login, is normally made possible because of cookies. This usage data gives insight as to what areas may need improvement, what areas customers have the most interest, or if some areas are not working properly.
The Cookies We Set
Account related cookies If you create an account with us then we will use cookies for the management of the signup process and general administration.
Login related cookies We use cookies when you are logged in so that we can remember this fact. This prevents you from having to log in every single time you visit a new page.
Orders processing related cookies This site offers e-commerce capabilities and some cookies are essential to ensure that your order is remembered between pages so that we can process it properly.
Site preferences cookies Some areas of the Website provide the ability for preferences you have chosen to be remembered. In order to make this possible, we need to set cookies so that this information can be called whenever you interact with a page is affected by your preferences.
Third Party Cookies
We also use cookies provided by trusted third parties. The following section details which third party cookies you might encounter through this site.
Google Analytics Our website uses Google Analytics which is one of the most widespread and trusted analytics solution on the web for helping us to understand how you use the website and help us find ways that we can improve your experience. These cookies may track things such as how long you spend on the site and the pages that you visit. As we sell products it's important for us to understand statistics about how many of the visitors to our site make a purchase and as such this is the kind of data that these cookies will track. Accurately tracking this helps us make business decisions about our advertising and product costs. Keeping our costs down help ensure the we offer best possible price.You can opt-out of having made your activity available to Google Analytics by installing the Google Analytics opt-out browser add-on, available at https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout/. The add-on prevents the Google Analytics JavaScript (ga.js, analytics.js, and dc.js) from sharing information with Google Analytics about visits activity.Google’s ability to use and share information collected by Google Analytics about your visits to this site is restricted by the Google Analytics Terms of Service, available at http://www.google.com/analytics/terms/us.html, and the Google Privacy Policy, available at http://www.google.com/policies/privacy/. To learn more about how Google collects and processes data in connection with Google Analytics, visit http://www.google.com/policies/privacy/partners/
Disabling Cookies
You can prevent the setting of cookies by adjusting the settings on your browser (see your browser Help for how to do this). Be aware that disabling cookies will affect the functionality of our Website. We recommend that you do not disable cookies on our Website.
"Do Not Track" Signals
Do Not Track is a preference you can set in your web browser to inform websites that you do not want to be tracked. There currently is no industry standard for websites and browsers to effectively honor Do Not Track requests. Because of this we do not support Do Not Track ("DNT") and our Website will ignore any Do Not Track requests made. If the industry later develops a standardized method to respond to these requests we will re-evaluate our position on this.
Service Providers
We may employ third party companies and individuals to facilitate sales of our products ("Service Providers"). These third parties have access to your Personal Data only to perform these tasks on our behalf and are obligated not to disclose or use it for any other purpose.
Payment Providers
For the security of your payment card information, we do not store or collect your payment card numbers. We use third-party payment services who specialize in securely storing and processing this information. When ordering from Zefon your payment card information is provided directly to one of these third-party payment services whose use of your personal information is governed by their Privacy Policy. These providers adhere to the standards set by PCI-DSS as managed by the PCI Security Standards Council, which is a joint effort of brands like Visa, Mastercard, American Express and Discover. PCI-DSS requirements help ensure the secure handling of payment information.
Marketing Service Providers
Zefon uses third-party providers for email marketing services. Zefon is in control over this data and the third-party providers do not have access or permission to use this data, which consists only of name and email address.
Transfer of Data
Your information, including Personal Data, may be transferred to — and maintained on — computers located outside of your state, province, country or other governmental jurisdiction where the data protection laws may differ than those from your jurisdiction.
If you are located outside United States and choose to provide information to us, please note that we transfer the data, including Personal Data, to the United States and process it there.
Your consent to this Privacy Policy followed by your submission of such information represents your agreement to that transfer.
Zefon International Inc will take all steps reasonably necessary to ensure that your data is treated securely and in accordance with this Privacy Policy and no transfer of your Personal Data will take place to an organization or a country unless there are adequate controls in place including the security of your data and other personal information.
Disclosure of Data
Business Transaction
If Zefon International Inc is involved in a merger, acquisition or asset sale, your Personal Data may be transferred. We will provide notice before your Personal Data is transferred and becomes subject to a different Privacy Policy.
Disclosure for Law Enforcement
Under certain circumstances, Zefon International Inc may be required to disclose your Personal Data if required to do so by law or in response to valid requests by public authorities (e.g. a court or a government agency).
Legal Requirements
Zefon International Inc may disclose your Personal Data in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to:
To comply with a legal obligation.
To protect and defend the rights or property of Zefon International Inc.
To prevent or investigate possible wrongdoing in connection with using the Website.
To protect against legal liability.
Security of Data
This website uses the Transport Layer Security (TLS) method to encrypt data transmissions. This encryption is secured using a certificate issued by Comodo. Please click on the Comodo Logo which will verify the validity of our Comodo Certificate, and our commitment to your security.
Legal Basis for Processing Personal Data Under General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR)
If you are from the European Economic Area (EEA), Zefon International Inc’s legal basis for collecting and using the personal information described in this Privacy Policy depends on the Personal Data we collect and the specific context in which we collect it.
Zefon International Inc may process your Personal Data because:
We need it to perform a contract with you (purchase of products).
You have given us permission to do so.
The processing is in our legitimate interests and it's not overridden by your rights.
For payment processing purposes.
To comply with the law.
Your Data Protection Rights Under General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR)
If you are a resident of the European Economic Area (EEA), you have certain data protection rights. Zefon International Inc aims to take reasonable steps to allow you to correct, amend, delete, or limit the use of your Personal Data.
In certain circumstances, you have the following data protection rights:
The right to be informedWe are providing by means of this privacy policy details of the information we collect and how we use the information.
The right to accessYou can access your personal information on our website at any time by logging in and going to the My Account section. If you are unable to perform these actions yourself, please contact us to assist you.
The right of rectificationYou can update your personal information on our website at any time by logging in and going to the My Account section. If you are unable to perform these actions yourself, please contact us to assist you.
The right of erasureIf you wish to delete your website account completely, please contact us to handle this for you. Please be advised that if you request deletion of your account, we can no longer do business with you as this is necessary to properly process transactions.
The right of restrictionYou have the right to request that we restrict the processing of your personal information. Please be advised that if you request restriction of processing, we can no longer do business with you as this is necessary to properly process transactions.
The right to data portabilityYou have the right to be provided with a copy of the information we have on you in a structured, machine-readable and commonly used format. While you may request this, please be aware the information you will receive is the same information you can see by logging into the website and going to the My Account section.
The right to objectYou have the right to object to our processing of your Personal Data. Please be advised that if object to the processing of your Personal Data, we can no longer do business with you as this is necessary to properly process transactions.
The right to request manual review in relation to automated decision makingYou have the right to request a manual review when automated decision-making processes are used. Zefon does not use any automated decision-making processes at this time.
Please note that we may ask you to verify your identity before responding to such requests.
You have the right to complain to a Data Protection Authority about our collection and use of your Personal Data. For more information, please contact your local data protection authority in the European Economic Area (EEA).
Links to Other Sites
Our Website may contain links to other sites that are not operated by us. If you click on a third party link, you will be directed to that third party's site. We have no control over and assume no responsibility for the content, privacy policies or practices of any third party sites or services. We advise you to review the Privacy Policy of every site you visit.
Children's Privacy
Our website does not address anyone under the age of 18 ("Children").
We do not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from anyone under the age of 18. If you are a parent or guardian and you are aware that your child has provided us with Personal Data, please contact us. If we become aware that we have collected Personal Data from children without verification of parental consent, we take steps to remove that information from our servers.
Changes to This Privacy Policy
We may revise our Privacy Policy from time to time. Revised policies will be effective as of the published effective date at the top of this policy. If the revision includes a substantial change, we will provide 30 days until it becomes effective and let you know by placing a prominent notice on our Website and/or via email.
Contact Us
If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please contact us:
By Email: ZefonCS@zefon.com
By Mail: Zefon International Inc. 5350 SW 1st Lane, Ocala, FL 34474, USA
AP Buck Inc.
Need Assistance?
Call +1 352 854 8080
Your details are safe!
100% secure payment
Newsletter
Wait...
+1-800-282-0073 (US)
Copyright © 2020 Zefon International. All Rights Reserved. | An ISO 9001-2015 Certified Company.
